var quizQuestions = [
    {
        //question 1
      question:
        "1. During the Saiyan Saga, how does Goku reach King Kai's planet?",
      choices: [
        "By making a wish with the Dragon Balls",
        "Via high speed vechicle",
        "By traveling along snake road",
        "By teleporting there instantly"],
      correctAnswer: "By traveling along snake road",
      image: "./assets/images/snakeroad.webp"
    },
    {
        //question 2
      question:
        "2. What item is used to restore a wounded Z fighter to full health?",
      choices: [
        "Z Sword",
        "Saiyan Hair",
        "Capsole Corp Medicine",
        "Senzu Beans"],
      correctAnswer: "Senzu Beans",
      image: "./assets/images/senzubean.webp"
  
    },
    {
      //question 3
    question:
      "3. What's the highest Super Saiyan level attained by Vegeta in DBZ?",
    choices: [
      "Super Saiyan 1",
      "Super Saiyan 2",
      "Super Saiyan 3",
      "Super Saiyan 4"],
    correctAnswer: "Super Saiyan 2",
    image: "./assets/images/vegetassj2.webp"
  },
  {
      //question 4
    question:
      "4. Who does Captain Ginyu serve?",
    choices: [
      "Cell",
      "Freiza",
      "Lord Slug",
      "Turles"],
    correctAnswer: "Freiza",
    image: "./assets/images/freiza.webp"
  },
  {
      //question 5
    question:
      "5. What does it do?",
    choices: [
      "It robs the opponent of half their strength",
      "It gives the wearer extra powers",
      "It reveals the power level of an opponent",
      "It reveals the power level of the wearer"],
    correctAnswer: "It reveals the power level of an opponent",
    image: "./assets/images/scanning.webp"
  },
  {
      //question 6
    question:
      "6. What's Goku's wife's name?",
    choices: [
      "Cha Chi",
      "Cho Cha",
      "Chi Cha",
      "Chi Chi"],
    correctAnswer: "Chi Chi",
    image: "./assets/images/chichi.webp"
  },
  {
      //question 7
    question:
      "7. Where is Goku when he transforms into a Super Saiyan for the first time?",
    choices: [
      "Planet Vegeta",
      "Planet Earth",
      "King Kai's Planet",
      "Planet Namek"],
    correctAnswer: "Planet Namek",
    image: "./assets/images/gokussj.webp"
  },
  {
      //question 8
    question:
      "8. What planet does Vegeta come from?",
    choices: [
      "Planet Z103",
      "Planet Vegeta",
      "Planet Freiza",
      "Planet of the Z"],
    correctAnswer: "Planet Vegeta",
    image: "./assets/images/planetvegeta.webp"
  },
  {
      //question 9
    question:
      "9. What power level does Vegeta freak over?",
    choices: [
      "5,000",
      "12,000",
      "9,000+",
      "10"],
    correctAnswer: "9,000+",
    image: "./assets/images/vegetascouter.webp"
  },
  {
      //question 10
    question:
      "10. Who is the most powerful villain of the series?",
    choices: [
      "Cell",
      "Boo",
      "Freiza",
      "Android 20"],
    correctAnswer: "Boo",
    image: "./assets/images/boo.webp"
  },
  ];